<resources>
    <string name="app_name">fragmentnavication</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="large_text">
        "Material is the metaphor.\n\n"
    </string>
    <string name="intro_page_one_one">
    "Quantum physics is the study of \n matter and energy at an atomic and subatomic level."
    </string>
    <string name="intro_page_one_two">
    "Apparently, objects at a macroscopic level and fundamental level do act differently. \n\n"
    "The understanding of these unique characteristics can then be applied \n to develop our pre-existing technology and methods. \n\n"
    </string>
    <string name="next">
        "Next >"
    </string>
    <string name="previous">
         "&lt; Previous"
    </string>
    <string name="superposition">1. SUPERPOSITION:</string>
<string name="intro_page_two_head">Some essential concepts related to quantum physics include:
</string>
    <string name="intro_page_two_superposition">
        "Quantum particles can be in different states at the same time.\n\n This characteristic is extremely useful for quantum computers.\n

    </string>
    <string name="intro_page_two_superposition_2">
    "A quantum computer contains qubits (quantum bits) which represent both binary values (0 and 1) at the same time, \n"
    </string>
    <string name = "intro_page_two_superposition_3">
    "allowing certain processes to be done much faster in quantum computers
    compared to classic computers. \n
        (Classic bits can only store either\n 0  or 1 at a certain time.)"
    </string>
    <string name="uncertainty"> "2. Uncertainty Principle"</string>
    <string name="uncertainty_one">"Measuring one property of a quantum particle would disturb its other properties. \n
        Therefore, two properties of a particle cannot be precisely known at the same time."
</string>
    <string name="entanglement">"3. Entanglement"</string>
    <string name="entanglement_1">"Quantum particles have a special connection called entanglement.
        To precisely describe the properties of a quantum particle, the other connected particles also need to be observed. \n
        Obtaining information of one particle
        would allow you to understand another connected particle."
</string>
    <string name="last_intro">"The growth in the study of quantum mechanics allow us to:
    better secure communication among devices,"
    </string>
    <string name="last_intro_2">"but at the same time also opens up an opportunity for hackers
    to easily penetrate existing encryption methods."</string>

    <string name="last_intro_3"> "This application will provide information regarding the usages of quantum physics in both perspectives."</string>


    <string name="tips">"(Please check the menu bar on the top left to advance to other sections.)"</string>


</resources>